leadfusion.com 2011-11-28

# Leadfusion, Inc. - financial calculators and email marketing solutions

## We respect and protect the privacy of those who visit or use our website. We want you to know how your information is used.

The following principles govern our information practices and other privacy aspects of our website:

  * Collection of information
  * Use of information
  * Sharing of information
  * Choice to Opt-out
  * Security of Information
  * Updating and Correcting Personal Information
  * Notification of Changes
  * Use by Children
  * Third Party Privacy Practices
  * Contacting Leadfusion

## Collection of Information

Leadfusion is the sole owner of all information collected on [www.leadfusion.com](http://www.leadfusion.com/) (the "website"). Leadfusion may collect information from our website visitors at different locations on our website; including but not limited to the following:

_Forms_  
There are various forms contained throughout the website including but not limited to Request for Product and Pricing Information, Technical Support Request, and Feedback Forms which are designed to collect certain information. These forms may collect the visitors' information, including but not limited to name, address, phone, title, email address, visitor's Leadfusion's name, visitor's Leadfusion's URL, and comments entered into the forms.

_Product Demonstrations_  
Leadfusion product demonstrations will perform calculations and return results based on financial, demographic, age identifiers, and other data input by the visitor. The input data is collected by Leadfusion.

_Customer Login_  
Authorized Leadfusion clients can log into Leadfusion's administrative website by   
entering their account name and password to verify their identity and establish a secure connection when logging into the administrative area. Activity performed on the administrative website is captured by Leadfusion for auditing and tracking purposes and to provide services to client.

_Log Files_  
Like most standard website servers, Leadfusion uses log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service providers (ISP), referring and exit pages, platform type, date and time stamp, number of clicks to analyze trends, track visitor movement in the aggregate, gather broad demographic information, and general site administration. This data is automatically collected when you use our Products and pages relating to such Products. Data collected in log files are not linked to personally identifiable information, such as name, address, email, etc. However, personally identifiable information may be collected when you provide such information to us.

_Cookies_  
Leadfusion's website and Products may use "cookies" which are placed on visitor's personal computers. For example, cookies used in Products enable data persistence so that visitors do not have to re-enter their information when utilizing more then one Product or when returning to use Product at a later time.

[Back to top]

## Use of Information

Information collected by Leadfusion on the website will be used to contact the visitor in direct response to their inquiry or for marketing purposes. Visitors who do not choose to 'opt-out' of future communications may receive future notification about Leadfusion products. Contact from Leadfusion includes:

  * _Visitor Requests and Feedback_ \- Leadfusion will contact visitors upon request when they submit a form. Visitors who do not choose to opt-out may receive future notification about Leadfusion products and services.

  * _Client Service Messages_ \- We communicate with clients on a regular basis to provide requested services or service notifications. With regard to issues relating to their account we reply via email or phone.

[Back to top]

## Sharing of Information

_Legal Disclaimer_  
Though we make every effort to preserve visitor privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our website.

_Third Parties_  
We DO NOT Share Personal Information with third parties (i) unless such parties are providing a service for Leadfusion; (ii) in the event of a business transition as set forth below; or (iii) if required to do so by law.

_Business Transitions_  
In the event that Leadfusion goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition, a sale of all or a portion of its assets, visitors' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

[Back to top]

## Choice to Opt-out

Customers who no longer wish to receive communications about future Leadfusion products and services may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to the email with "unsubscribe" in the subject line, or by emailing us at [privacy@leadfusion.com](mailto:privacy@leadfusion.com). The visitor may also call toll-free at 1-877-205-9825, or write to Leadfusion, Inc., Attn: Contract Administrator, 12707 High Bluff Drive, Ste. 325, San Diego, CA 92130.

[Back to top]

## Security of Information

At Leadfusion we take precautions in accordance with industry standards to protect our visitors' information. When a visitor submits information via our website, their information is protected both online and off-line.

When our clients are logged into the administrative area managing their licensed products, their activities are protected by a 128-bit SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption technology. While we use SSL encryption to protect information online, we also protect visitor and client information off-line in accordance with industry standards. Nevertheless, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure and while Leadfusion strives to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee or warrant that it will remain secure. You agree that Leadfusion shall not be held responsible for harm that you or any person may suffer as a result of a breach of confidentiality in respect to your use of the Leadfusion's website or Products or any information that is collected or that you transmit to us.

[Back to top]

## Updating and Correcting Personal Information

If a client's personally identifiable information changes (such as Leadfusion contact, phone, email or postal address), they can email us at [support@leadfusion.com](mailto:support@leadfusion.com), call us toll-free at 1-877-205-9825, or write to us at Leadfusion, Attn: Customer Services, 12707 High Bluff Drive, Ste. 325, San Diego, CA 92130.

[Back to top]

## Notification of Changes

Leadfusion reserves the right to change this privacy policy without notice. If, however, we are going to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify visitors and clients via email. Visitors and clients will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. However, if a visitor or client has opted out of all communication with Leadfusion, they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this different manner.

[Back to top]

## Use by Children

Because of the financial nature of our business, the Leadfusion website ("website") is not designed to appeal to children under the age of 13. Therefore, we do not knowingly attempt to solicit or receive any information from children. If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, please email [privacy@leadfusion.com](mailto:privacy@leadfusion.com), call toll-free at 1-877-205-9825, or write to Leadfusion, Inc., Attn: Contract Administrator, 12707 High Bluff Drive, Ste. 325, San Diego, CA 92130.

[Back to top]

## Third Party Privacy Practices

Our website may contain links to websites operated and maintained by other third parties over which we have absolutely no control. Any information you provide to third parties will be governed by the terms of each third party's privacy policy, if any, and we encourage you to investigate and ask questions before disclosing any information to third parties. YOUR ACCESS TO AND USE OF ANY LINKED WEBSITES IS SOLELY AT YOUR OWN RISK. YOU AGREE THAT LEADFUSION HAS NO RESPONSIBILITY OR LIABILITY WHATSOEVER FOR THE CONTENT, ACTIONS OR POLICIES OF ANY OTHER PARTY. THE INCLUSION OF THIRD PARTY WEBSITES IN CONNECTION WITH THIS WEBSITE OR OUR PRODUCTS IN NO WAY CONSTITUTES AN ENDORSEMENT OF SUCH THIRD PARTY WEBSITE'S CONTENT, ACTIONS OR POLICIES.

[Back to top]

## Contacting Leadfusion

If website visitors or clients have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy statement or our information practices, please contact us at:

Email: [privacy@leadfusion.com](mailto:privacy@leadfusion.com)  
Phone: 858-259-2100  

Postal Address:  
Leadfusion, Inc.   
Attn: Contract Administrator  
12707 High Bluff Drive, Ste. 325  
San Diego, CA  92130

[Back to top]
